Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
We swap in parts from Fords...
...Plymouths and Cadillacs.
My grandfather bought it in 1957.
When he died. it passed to my father.
Then my brother. and now to me.
Look at this.
This is an engine from a boat.
- (IN ENGLISH) No way!
- MAN: Yeah. (CONTINUING IN SPANISH)
Whatever it takes to keep it running.
(IN ENGLISH) This is the Cuban spirit.
(CONTINUING IN SPANISH)
Your spirit.
Don't ever lose that.
Dom. Dom. (IN SPANISH)
It's your cousin.
He's in trouble.
Come on!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) You know I can't
make a living without my car.
Not my problem. bro.
Dominic Toretto. I heard about you.
Welcome to my island.
Why you hookin' up my cousin's car?
He needed money. I gave it to him.
He can't pay. I take the car.
I just need a few more days.
"Few more days" wasn't part of the deal.
Come on. You make a deal.
you gotta live up to it.
You make a deal. you gonna live up to it.
"Gonna" live up to it?
Oh. so you're one of those types.
You take everyone's ride.
and then ship it back to the States?
(IN SPANISH)
You should show your people some respect.
(IN ENGLISH) You watch your mouth.
(CHUCKLES)
Now you got a problem.
- I'm gonna keep it about the cars.
- (IN SPANISH)
I'm really scared.
(IN ENGLISH)
You want a car. get it the right way.
How?
Race for it.
I already own it. bro.
Not that car.
Mine.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
Dom. his car is
the fastest car on the island.
Do you know what he has under that hood?
He knows it doesn't matter
what's under a hood.
The only thing that matters
is who's behind the wheel.
You think so?
I know so.
Then race his car.
And we ain't racing no quarter-mile. here.
We race the Cuban mile.
Done.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I appreciate what you're trying to do.
but my car is the slowest car on the island.
Was.
Pull the seats. the doors. the battery...
If it ain't the motor. take it off.
Laughing gas?
Nah. Fed. This is Cuban NOS.
You guys are crazy.
What are you doing?
DOM: Poor man's turbo.
Pull the vacuum line and hold on.
Old trick that Buster used to play.
in case of emergencies.
You know that's way too much
boost for that engine.
DOM: It's gonna be fast.
It's gonna be a bomb.
Only needs to go a mile.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(IN SPANISH)
Are you ready for this. my family?
This is Havana!
Be fast.
Be safe.
But don't be last. Racers ready!
Vamonos!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
(IN ENGLISH)
That car belongs in the trash. bro!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(HORN BLARING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
- FERNANDO: Where are they going?
- LETTY: I don't know. Let's go!
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Ghost him.
MAN: Sí.
(PEOPLE YELLING)
Adiós. Toretto!
Okay. Buster.
Let's see if this works.
- (TIRES SQUEALING)
- (ENGINE REVVING)
That's impossible.
(ALL CHEERING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CHEERING)
(IN ENGLISH) Look out!
(ALL CONTINUE CHEERING)
A deal's a deal.
You won my car.
And you earned my respect.
Keep your car.
Your respect is good enough for me.
DOM: Yo. cousin...
Sorry about your car.
Yours was too slow for a Toretto. anyway.
Your Impala? Are you serious?
(ALL CHEERING)
Look at that smile.
I love it when you smile.
You make me happy.
Mmm. I think this place makes you happy.
It's like it speaks to you.
You remember that guy. the racer and his dad?
The one with the boat engine under the hood?
Yeah!
- Yes.
- Of course.
I was looking at them. and I...
And I couldn't help but to imagine
what you'd be like if you were a dad.
No. no. no! I'm not pregnant.
Is that what you want?
It's not about what I want or what you want.
It's about why we haven't asked the question.
(ENGINE CRANKS SLOWLY)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
- (IN ENGLISH) What?
- You need a hand?
Yeah. I think I do.
- Sounds like you're not getting any fuel.
- Yeah?
Probably the shut-off solenoid.
Let's see if we can get some power to it.
What brings you to Cuba?
The same thing that brings
everyone else to Cuba.
Culture. people. the beauty.
What brings you to Cuba?
- Work.
- Must be casual Friday.
How's that honeymoon going. Dom?
Your fuel relay is missing.
I know.
I love to play games.
I've beaten the best of 'em.
But I'm kind of in a rush.
so if you've got something to say to me...
Oh. this is a very different game.
that I can assure you.
This... There's something
much greater at work here.
This is fate.
I choose to make my own fate.
Not today.
Is this the road you take
to your apartment every morning?
What else is different. Dom?
Was Santiago's closed?
Did you have to cross two blocks
to go get your Cuban coffees?
What is it. black. no sugar?
Yeah.
I put a lot of work into
getting you here today.
Well. now that I'm here. what do you want?
I want you to work for me.
Work for you?
Oh. I could've saved you a lot of time. then.
See. I don't work for anyone.
You can't walk away from this. Dom.
We're gonna have this conversation.
one way or the other.
You see. that's the funny thing about fate.
It's cunning.
It can bring you beautiful things.
and it can also bring you moments like this.
Oh. you're gonna want to work for me.
You're gonna betray your brothers.
abandon your code. and shatter your family.
You see. your team is about to go up
against the only thing they can't handle.
What's that?
You.
Oh. and. Dom.
I wouldn't mention this to anyone.
(ENGINE STARTS)
HOBBS: They are gonna be hitting us
with everything they got.
So we wanna engage with maximum speed.
Neutralize their shooters.
and then move on to our objective.
There's two things
I want you to keep in mind.
Number one. I chose you for this squad
because you are the most
fearsome warriors on the planet.
And number two. you go out there.
you do your job. and you take 'em down.
Everyone. And I mean everyone.
Mani's and pedi's at the mall later on today.
(ALL CHEERING)
Huh?
- (WHISTLE BLOWING)
- GIRLS: Monarchs!
(CHANTING HAKA)
(ALL CHANTING HAKA)
(EXCLAIMS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(WHISPERS) What?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
I don't wanna play anymore.
All right. let's go. girls.
Let's go. let's go!
Final two minutes.
DS ALLAN: Quite the cheering section.
HOBBS: Oh. yeah.
Yeah. it's the moms.
They come out to support the kids.
Except there seem to be more moms than kids.
Way more moms.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
(CHUCKLES) Yeah. It's a big soccer town.
Let's go. girls!
So. your intel was spot-on.
That Damocles 7 EMP weapon
that went missing in the Gulf?
Arms dealers from the Liberation
Front have it in Berlin.
HOBBS: Shit!
This thing can wipe out
an entire electrical grid in a major city.
No lights. no power.
Instant Stone Age.
Chloe. Maya.
you can't let her run by you like that.
- Let's go. let's go! Cross!
- Agent Hobbs. this is a Class Four WMD.
Do you have any idea what's at stake here?
Yes. I know exactly
what is at stake here. okay?
If the Pink Butterflies beat my Red Dragons.
that means we lose the championship.
Which means I have 20 little girls who
are crying. and that's not a good thing.
Which then means I have to spend
a lot of time in ice-cream shops
and a lot of time at Tay Tay concerts.
Tay Tay?
Taylor Swift. Gotta be shittin' me.
Get it together. okay?
Let's go. girls!
We need you to do this.
It's a lot of lives at stake.
All right. but I need to be clear here.
The US government cannot sanction
this operation in any way.
- You're on your own.
- Hey.
If this thing goes sideways.
you don't just get burned.
You go to prison.
And there's nothing we can do to get you out.
Let me tell you something.
The only thing that I love more
than saving lives is my daughter.
So. if you don't shut up
with this government bullshit right now.
and start showing some team spirit
and respect for the Red Dragons.
I'm gonna have all 20 of them line up
and kick you right in the tay-tay.
Go Dragons!
Say it again.
Attaboy. Go Dragons.
- Go Dragons.
- (CROWD EXCLAIMS)
- SAM: I'm open.
- She's open! Go. go!
Yes! (LAUGHING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
That is my daughter right there. Yes.
Yes. come here.
How did I do?
Awesome.
Nice job. kid.
- (HOBBS SIGHS)
- Daddy's gotta go to work?
Uh. yeah. Daddy's gotta go to work.
Now. you're gonna need
to get a team you can trust.
Oh. I already got one.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(SIGHS)
HOBBS: Hey. Dom.
Hey. Hobbs.
I got a job in Berlin
and I need a favor. brother.
No problem.
I'll grab the team and meet you in Berlin.
Thanks. man. I'll see you soon.
(GRUNTS)
You were only supposed
to create a diversion. Roman.
That was a diversion!
How many of the damn explosives did you use?
ROMAN: I don't know. Tej.
- All of it?
- Wait. all of it?
Roman. Jesus Christ.
We got more of your fan club ahead.
They're still on us!
These guys are taking this personal.
Roman. we just blew up their facility
and stole their EMP.
Other than your doctor's cold finger.
I'd say it's about as personal as it can get.
Phase Two!
Phase Two? So you just
gonna keep that to yourself?
What happened to Phase One?
What about that part?
Yeah. Remember the airplane?
Everyone drove their cars out but you?
I told you. my engine seized up.
It's your balls that seized up.
Just follow my lead. okay?
And. Roman. whatever you do. don't think.
Huh?
Tej. drop it!
Bombs away.
(BEEPS)
Split. now!
ROMAN: Holy...
(CURSES IN GERMAN)
ROMAN: (OVER RADIO) Great plan. Tej.
But just so you know. you missed some.
Oh. just wait for it.
ROMAN: Oh. shit!
I hate you. Tej!
(LAUGHS)
Got your ass.
You good?
I'll see you when it's done.
All right. great job. team.
Let's break off and meet me
at the safe house.
(ENGINE REVVING)
A hell of a job. brother.
When we get back to the base.
the beer's on me.
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
You lost your goddamn mind. Toretto?
Toretto. you put hands on that thing.
you're gonna have the whole world
gunning for you. including me.
(DOM GRUNTS)
I don't know what you're doing.
but you better think about this. Toretto.
It ain't too late to stop this.
It is now.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
That sumbitch just crossed us.
- What?
- Wait a second. what are you talking about?
Dom took the EMP.
Bullshit.
Where are you?
HOBBS: It's too late for me. Get outta here.
Saw that look in his eye.
and I've seen that look before.
Dominic Toretto just went rogue.
TEJ:
All right. I got his phone records. y'all.
It's a whole bunch of calls
to untraceable numbers.
ROMAN: Burner phones. right?
TEJ: Nah. scrambler.
Same number. but they got some sort
of micro-router to bury the signal path.
which means Dom is clearly communicating
with somebody that's above our pay grade.
Look. I don't know Dom as well as you.
but if we just look at the facts.
Dom's been having highly
encrypted conversations
with some mysterious person.
He took out Hobbs.
He stole an EMP. Now he's disappeared.
So. what are you saying?
Maybe we should consider
the fact that Hobbs is right.
Dom did go rogue.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
ROMAN: Letty.
LETTY: Before you judge the man.
remember. you're breathing right
now because he saved your life.
You just gonna let her bump
your shoulder like that?
I'm just saying.
that was a little aggressive.
What you gonna do. email her?
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) Check.
(CELL DOOR BUZZING)
Moment. will you. fellas?
Thank you.
Well. this is an exciting new look.
It's a little tight in the crotch. as always.
(CHUCKLES)
What boy-band bus did she fall out of?
It's my new junior associate.
He's working with me on this. All yours.
Mr. Nobody and I have been given
the authority to get you out of this.
All you have to do is agree
to the terms and you're free.
What's training wheels talking about?
What terms?
Confess to your crimes in Berlin.
Treason. international espionage.
massive destruction of civic property.
You do that. we close the case.
- And?
- And the DSS blacklists you.
Germany loves that.
LITTLE NOBODY:
Officially. you will be a criminal.
MR. NOBODY: Wait. Whoa. whoa. whoa.
You need to work on your delivery. all right?
Unofficially...
You're off the books. You come work with me.
I'm not a criminal.
MR. NOBODY: Luke. come on. Labels.
There is no confession.
There are no backroom deals.
I got myself into this.
I'm gonna get myself out of it.
- You know that.
- I do. and that's what I told him. (SIGHS)
Well. there you have it.
Good luck in the courts. man.
What about your daughter?
You know. if you're not gonna do it for
your country. at least do it for your kid.
(CHUCKLES) Big mistake. kid.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hold on. Luke. Luke.
He's still working from the manual.
I mean. he doesn't even
really know the rules.
Now. come on. give him a break.
(STRAINED) Give me a break.
Luke.
(GRUNTING)
Appreciate it.
(COUGHING)
It's good to see you. Nobody.
You. too.
Rule number one...
Know your audience.
I gave you your shot. You shit the bed.
Now I'm gonna show you how to get this done.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
You're dead. cop. Dead!
INMATE: I'm gonna slice
some bacon off your back. pig.
DECKARD: Well. well. well...
Luke Hobbs behind bars.
Would you look at that.
The bent cop got his day.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(CELL DOOR BUZZING)
You know. that color looks good on you.
Yeah. it'll look a whole hell of a lot
better with your blood on it.
Yeah. good luck with that. Hercules.
Lawman gone bad. huh?
Such a cliche.
Oh. well. welcome to the club.
I wouldn't get that twisted. son.
We ain't in no club.
we got nothing in common.
And unlike you. I ain't gonna be here long.
What. you bring a shovel. did you?
Because it's 38 feet of steel and concrete.
Or so I've been told.
(DECKARD CHUCKLES)
Better get to digging.
Wanker.
Yeah.
Move.
Say that again.
If I say it again. it'll be to a corpse.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm gonna enjoy this.
CIPHER: Welcome back. Dom.
Nice job out there.
You excited about tonight?
You're going on this?
You're with me. Dom.
Showing me your shoe collection?
Yep.
A pair for every occasion.
You have enough guns in here
to outfit a small army. huh?
Oh. this is just the tip of the iceberg.
You know what I like about you. Dom?
You're a genuine outlaw.
I mean. you're a man
who lives by his own rules.
Which is surprising.
because when I saw you in Cuba.
I heard about a guy who almost
killed you with a motorcycle.
and you let him keep his car?
Oh. that confused you?
Hmm.
'Course I could've taken his car.
But it's about something bigger.
This way...
I changed him.
That's not your responsibility.
- But it's who I am.
- Is it?
Let me ask you something. Dom.
What's the best thing in your life?
- Family.
- No. it's not.
Not if you're being honest.
It's the 10 seconds between start and finish.
when you're not thinking about anything.
No family. no obligations.
Just you.
Being free.
I gotta tell you.
this whole saving-the-world. Robin Hood
nonsense you've been doing recently?
It's bullshit. It's not you.
Be who you are.
Why live only a quarter mile at a time
when you can live your whole life that way?
(PANTING)
Is that it?
Is that all those
bloated-out muscles will give ya?
All show and no go.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Oh. I got plenty of go.
You must've misplaced that when I kicked
your arse up and down that office of yours.
Yeah.
Just like you Brits. rewriting history. huh?
All I know is. it wasn't me that was
thrown out of a four-story window.
Jumped.
I jumped out of a four-story window.
saving my partner's life.
'Cause where I'm from.
we don't settle fights by throwing bombs.
Well. that's funny. because where I'm from.
we don't need women to run to our rescue.
I mean. do you really believe
you can stand in front of me
and beat me in a straight-up.
old-fashioned fist fight?
Let me tell you something.
Me and you. one-on-one. no one else around.
I will beat your ass like a Cherokee drum.
Maybe one day we'll find out.
Oh. you better hope that day never comes.
(DOOR BUZZES)
I said no. Mr. Nobody.
I'm not leaving this cell.
I'll get out my way.
(ALARM BLARING)
The right way!
Hey! Why's the door open?
Get back in your cell!
Relax. It's just a malfunction.
- Get back!
- HOBBS: Just a malfunction.
(GRUNTING)
Stop him! Don't let him get away!
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
MILLER: Hobbs!
I've been waiting a long time for this.
Keep waiting. bitch.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Rubber bullets. Big mistake.
(GROANING)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Well. that took longer than I expected.
- HOBBS: Two questions.
- MR. NOBODY: Yeah.
- My daughter?
- With your sister.
- Toretto?
- (CHUCKLES)
It's interesting you ask.
This is my new base. Welcome to nowhere.
It's a little sterile for you.
(CHUCKLES)
Listen. there's something
I wanna talk to you about after.
Hey. listen. guys. Thanks...
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
What? Handcuffs? What is this?
It's called abuse of power.
You told me to round them up.
I didn't tell you to hand...
Cut 'em loose. Oh. man. This is embarrassing.
I'm sorry. guys. really. I...
So. this is how you treat old friends?
TEJ: Friends? We don't even really know
who the hell this guy is.
Doesn't matter who I am. Tej.
I'm. like. nobody. okay?
Nobody. So. then. who is he?
Him? He's nothing. He's. like. less than me.
Clearly. we're getting nowhere with nobody.
I've been in here for four hours.
and my ribs are showing.
I don't know about y'all. but I'm out.
- I wouldn't recommend that.
- What?
Well. thanks to your botched Berlin job.
you all made Interpol's
Top 10 Most Wanted list.
- Top 10.
- MR. NOBODY: Mmm-hmm.
That's all right.
- Well. not you. Roman.
- What do you mean?
You just missed the cut.
You're number 11. so...
- I'm... I missed?
- Yeah.
ROMAN: That's impossible!
What number did they come in at?
Six. eight. nine. ten.
- She's 10?
- Mmm-hmm.
That's impossible. There's no way she's a 10.
Oh. she's definitely a 10. (SCOFFS)
How about we focus on someone who
we're not gonna find on anybody's list.
We're awaiting hard confirmation.
but I believe that's the cyber
terrorist known as Cipher.
Wait. no. Cipher's an organization.
Not a person.
Not according to our sources.
What does she want?
No one knows.
Cipher is like a digital act of God.
They... Well. she can manipulate
world systems from the shadows.
Anything that can be hacked
is hers to play with.
And here's the kicker.
You'll never find her linked to any of it.
Her digital identity is scrubbed
every few seconds. worldwide.
So. basically. she's the bogeyman.
Damn. she's one of the hottest
bogeymans I've ever seen.
I mean. if y'all know her.
tell her to get at your boy.
- (ROMAN CHUCKLES)
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- What are you. 12?
- ROMAN: That was my shin. mother...
Let's just say. people are scared
of the hacker group Anonymous.
But even Anonymous won't mess with her.
What the hell does
any of this have to do with us?
Probably nothing. Letty.
but I do find it interesting that.
apparently. for some reason.
she's now working with this guy.
(SIGHS)
He's already delivered a fully
operational EMP into her hands.
Detonate that. they can turn any city
in the world into a war zone.
So. then. what is it you're suggesting we do?
MR. NOBODY: Maybe we find Dom. huh?
Well. first. let's catch him.
and then figure out why he's turned.
So. y'all want us to track Dom.
Yeah. I know. Roman. it's kind of a big job.
It's impossible.
Which is why I'm bringing in
an extra pair of hands.
Ah. my day just got
a whole hell of a lot better.
Mr. Nobody. you wanna tell me why
you just put me in a room with this
tea-and-crumpets eating. criminal sumbitch?
What a big mouth on a small head.
coming from Prisoner 6753.
Don't think we've forgotten
everything that you've done.
We are not teaming up with this guy.
Let's get one thing clear.
I ain't on your team.
I don't care about you.
your crew. or your little family.
I'm here for Cipher.
What are you gonna do.
apply for a job? Head Asshole?
You know. I think that tight T-shirt's
cutting off the circulation to your brain.
You should get a bigger size.
Cipher came to me first.
Wanted me to steal Nightshade for her.
When I said no. she went after my brother.
Ah. yes. brother Owen.
Who could forget him. huh?
Former hell-raiser and current guest
at a nasty little black site prison.
Cipher corrupted him and left him for dead.
So. if I get a shot to take her down.
believe me. Flex. I'm taking it.
You're taking my boot right up your ass.
is what you're taking.
Guys. guys. The fastest way
to find Cipher is through Toretto.
Now. aside from myself.
there's only two men in the world
that have ever managed to actually
track him down with any success.
And guess what. They're both
standing in front of me right now.
So. like it or not.
you two are gonna work together.
You got that?
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
Am I the only one seeing this?
Oh. this ought to be good.
(MUMBLES)
Use God's Eye.
We put our lives on the line.
running around the world
trying to figure this thing out.
It can find anybody. right?
Let's use it to find Dom.
Roman. that is a great idea.
Did you hear that? "Great idea."
No. no. no. don't tune it out. Huh?
Mr. Nobody. let's fire it up. huh?
TEJ: Got him. He's in London.
Yeah.
(BEEPING)
RAMSEY:
Wait. We've got a second match in Hong Kong.
ROMAN: Beijing and Seoul.
TEJ: And Tokyo.
RAMSEY: And just about every
other major city on the planet.
MR. NOBODY:
And so. God's Eye was where we started.
But Cipher's already created an evasion
that masks their location by pinging
random spots all over the globe.
but it was a good thought. Roman.
So. she's made my program obsolete.
And that. Ramsey. is why you're here.
See. simple solutions
aren't gonna cut it here. slick.
Why you look at me when you say that?
Wait a second. Wait. wait.
Simple solutions might just cut it.
You see. in order for God's Eye
to give off all these false pings.
means they have to be using a FLEA relay.
Watch these two.
Which means it has
a decaying sync randomizer.
Which we can reverse...
And track it back to the originating source
and find Dom's true location.
I'm telling you. they got skills.
That was my idea.
That's what I was saying. Remember in there?
All right. let's try this.
It's working.
Time you wanna check your manual
and start organizing a force response.
Let's get a hold of
our international assets...
He's still green.
Yeah. like fresh baby shit.
As soon as we have Toretto's location.
I want to mobilize.
Let's get a hold of a better asshole.
No one respects you...
(IMITATES RADIO STATIC) Cover.
Get away from me.
All right. they're not in China.
Or Russia.
Europe's clear.
But this one's not going away.
(BEEPING)
This is interesting.
Why?
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Because that's here.
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(MAN COUGHING)
CIPHER: (ECHOING) Did you all enjoy that?
Next-generation concussion grenade.
It scrambles your senses.
Don't worry. it'll wear off in an hour.
- (GROANING)
- Probably.
Hello. Deckard. Nice to see you again.
(LAUGHING) Look at this.
body's not even cold. Dom.
Your family's already replacing you.
You chose the losing team.
I guess your brother is smarter than you.
(DECKARD GRUNTING)
(BEEPING)
Smart move. embedding God's Eye
into the mainframe.
Irritating to make me have to come
all the way down here to get it. but...
Let's go.
(ALL GROANING)
Dom!
You're gonna turn your back
on family? Just like that?
Let's go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
HOBBS: You okay?
That wasn't him.
I don't know what she's got on him.
but that wasn't Dom.
Brian would know what to do.
No!
We can't bring Brian and Mia into this.
We agreed on that.
ROMAN: I know.
DOM: Back there. was that for her.
for me. or you?
And was it even necessary?
Necessary?
Nothing is necessary.
Everything is a choice.
And I simply made one. But so did you.
You could've stopped me.
but you chose not to.
I wonder what Letty thought about that.
The problem with putting
your foot on a tiger's neck
is you can never let it up.
I think I need to remind you
why you chose to be here.
(GASPS)
Elena.
ELENA: Dom?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have come.
Nothing could have kept me away.
Now she has the three of us.
(BABY COOING)
Do you wanna see him?
See Papa?
(BABY GURGLING)
See Papa.
Papa.
(COOING)
When I realized I was pregnant.
you had just found out Letty was alive.
So I decided when Letty and you got
back from your honeymoon.
I was going to tell you.
But then she took us before I had the chance.
(COOS)
His name?
(CONTINUES COOING)
I call him Marcos.
But that's his middle name.
I thought his father
should give him his first name.
I'm sorry. Dom.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
ELENA: Whatever happens.
just save our son.
Your son.
CIPHER: Good visit?
I know. I know what you're thinking.
I just let the guards go. so there's
only two opponents in the room.
Rhodes has the gun.
so you'll take him out first.
I know you.
And then you're thinking. Elena's a cop.
Maybe the two of you
can fight your way out of here.
(WHISPERS) So much to think about.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Let me make it easier for you.
Do with it as you wish.
Have you heard of Choice Theory. Dom?
There is a bunch of axioms.
but only two you really need
to concern yourself with.
One. the only person's behavior
we can control is our own.
And. two. the only thing we can truly give
another person is information.
So. let me give you some.
You see these cameras in here?
The moment you make a move.
highly-paid men with weapons
will make their way into this room
with one very specific instruction.
It's not to save me.
It's to kill your son.
Now. that's a lot of bullets.
and it only takes one
for you to lose everything.
So. I have to ask you.
because I know family is so important to you.
Is that really a choice you want to make?
Because I'm ready if you are.
If I pull this trigger.
and God knows I want to.
if I killed everyone on this plane.
I still couldn't get in there.
'Cause of your two-man fail-safe system.
Since I'm alone.
I got no choice!
I didn't think so.
You want to see the old Dom?
Watch.
(SOBBING)
Bitch.
- Don't. don't.
- Sweet dreams.
Please!
LITTLE NOBODY: Damn it.
She wiped it all. Took God's Eye.
That was the one thing
we could use to find them.
We lost everything.
What do you got. Princess?
Finding Toretto.
But I got a couple of minutes to spare.
if you want me to send you
to the hospital. Again.
(CHUCKLES) Yo. Rules.
First off. that's not my name.
- Little Nobody.
- Don't call me that.
Oh. that's definitely sticking.
Great. Do me a favor and tell Your Majesty
over there that we're gonna find Toretto.
We find Toretto together as a team.
And when this is all over with.
I'm happy to slap that
whisker biscuit right off his face.
Wait a minute. guys.
I think Deckard's actually onto something.
How do you think Dom and Cipher
got into the country without us knowing?
Ghost flights.
I thought untraceable aircraft
was all Internet conspiracy stuff.
MR. NOBODY: It's not.
Satellites and radar grids
all across the globe
shift like an ocean.
They've got channels that open and close.
And theoretically. if you know the right
people who know the right patterns...
You can fly right through the blind
spots completely undetected.
So you know where Dom is headed?
(LAPTOP BEEPS)
Yeah. New York.
(CHUCKLES)
You see there. Luke?
You guys are gonna get along just great.
Which proves rule number two.
you never lose everything.
Fire up the chopper.
Well. guys. have a ball in the Big Apple.
ROMAN:
And why are we traveling like this again?
TEJ: Because Dom took God's Eye.
so we need to stay off the grid.
ROMAN: But like this?
(ALL GRUNTING)
ROMAN: Look here. man.
Before I throw up in my mouth.
let me ask you. what are we doing here?
That's a good question. Roman.
Let me show you.
Welcome to our new base of operations.
No. seriously. What is this place?
This is heaven.
It's the agency garage.
They call it the Toy Shop.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LITTLE NOBODY:
This is where we house every vehicle
seized from drug dealers on the East Coast.
Now. Mr. Nobody said that if we're
gonna have a chance at catching Dom.
we're gonna have to be damn fast.
Figured this would help.
We got a tank.
750 horsepower.
6.6 liter. V8 Duramax engine
with an M153 CROWS remotely
operated weapon station on top.
You didn't get this from drug dealers.
LITTLE NOBODY: No. No. that. uh.
the United States Army lent me.
See. the Army's developing machines like this
that soldiers can drive from a mile away.
so they can stay safe and alive.
But. luckily. there's a backup driver's seat
for those of us that like
to get more "hands on."
ROMAN:
I'm sitting here wondering this whole time.
will this thing fit in valet
at Cheesecake Factory?
No one is getting "hands on."
She doesn't go on city streets.
Wow. I'm in love.
Again. no. no.
That's a million-dollar show car.
The point is to not draw attention.
It's reverse psychology.
Dom would never see it coming.
It's neon orange.
The International Space Station
would see it coming.
Go choose anything less conspicuous.
ROMAN: No. no. no. Calipers are my...
- This is ridiculous.
- Not happening.
Hey. my man.
you can put that down right there.
This is a gift. a real gift.
I know what you're doing.
(LAUGHS) I like your beard.
You're Blanta. Black Santa?
No. I'm serious. Put it down right there.
What are you doing?
Engine's misfiring. I gotta check it out.
No. that's not part of the plan. Dom.
DOM: Clearly.
But unless you want
the engine to seize on the job...
You have five minutes.
(MOUTHING) Five minutes.
I want another visual.
I got an ATM.
I don't like this.
I want to see Toretto.
- There are no more cameras.
- Then find something!
Punch in on something reflective.
A car mirror. anything.
Do you know who I am?
It's why I'm here.
Do you know what I'm capable of?
I'll give you until I finish me cuppa.
And I'm fucking thirsty.
I've got limited time.
so I won't take up too much of yours.
Oh. no.
No. you've already taken everything
I have of value. Mr. Toretto.
What more could you possibly want?
To give you something back.
Talk to me.
Something's not right here.
First time I saw my son
was behind a bulletproof glass.
When he reached for me. I couldn't hold him.
It's the worst pain I ever felt.
I know you know exactly how that feels.
Maybe we could change that.
Now. why do I think
you're about to suggest something
really dodgy. Mr. Toretto?
It's why I'm here.
Jesus. punch in on something.
I'm not liking this. Something's not right.
- Rhodes. you close?
- RHODES: Yeah.
CIPHER: Go.
The delivery truck's moving.
(MOUTHING) I know.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER RADIO)
HOBBS: "Captain Deckard Shaw
distinguished himself by acts of gallantry
"at the risk of his life above
and beyond the call of duty.
"His bold actions saved the lives
of hostages and his teammates.
"Recommendation: Victoria Cross."
Highest honor the British
government has ever given
to a traitor.
Something about this whole thing
that just doesn't add up to me.
Well. that would be
the same kind of funny math
that says a DSS agent who has
a Silver Star for valor stole an EMP.
Sound familiar. huh?
You want to give me a hand?
- On three?
- Yeah.
One. two. three.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You know what. Twinkle Toes?
In another life. I bet me and you
could've done some serious damage.
- Yeah. we could've.
- Yeah.
Shame I'm gonna have to bounce your head
off the fender when this is all over.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Ah. well. with all due respect. Captain.
when this whole thing is over.
we're gonna find a location.
and I'm gonna knock your teeth
so far down your throat.
you're gonna stick a toothbrush
right up your ass to brush them.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Give me God's Eye.
God's Eye. active.
Good.
Let's find us a Russian.
I spy with my little eye.
a Minister of Defense.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
We land back in Moscow by nine.
Here's the latest defense report.
All the items in yesterday's brief.
Upload those coordinates to Dom's nav.
Copy that.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
He's in the third car.
(OVER EARPIECE) It's a Guard Class limousine.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Where's my team?
- Where's his team?
- There's no sign of them yet.
They're off the grid.
They're probably just
bunkered down somewhere.
DOM: We're closing in on 'em.
You guys ready?
CIPHER: One thing I can guarantee.
Dom. no one's ready for this.
I want every chip with a zero-day
exploit in a two-mile radius
around that motorcade now.
There's over a thousand of them.
Hack 'em all.
(ENGINE STARTS)
It's zombie time.
I'd buckle up if I were you.
- (TIRES SQUEALING)
- Hmm?
WOMAN: (YELLS) What are you doing?
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(HORNS BLARING)
GOD'S EYE TECH: Safety sensors overridden.
Thank you.
(ENGINE STARTS)
MAN: Whoa.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(WOMAN SHRIEKING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(YELLS AND GROANS)
Hey!
Target the motorcade.
And here they come.
(IN RUSSIAN)
What is going on?
(IN ENGLISH) Ouch.
- (GRUNTS)
- (IN RUSSIAN)
Drive!
GOD'S EYE TECH: (IN ENGLISH)
Police escort down.
Take out the lead and follow cars.
(ENGINES STARTING)
(IN RUSSIAN)
Drive! Drive!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- Two more down.
- They're still under warranty.
(RUSSIAN SECRET SERVICE AGENT IN RUSSIAN)
There's more ahead of us.
Shoot their engines!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oh. God!
(MAN SCREAMING)
OFFICER: (OVER RADIO)
We got an army of cars driving themselves!
Send backup. send SWAT!
I don't care if you send
the goddamn Boy Scouts.
just send 'em some help!
Now. that's Dom.
(IN RUSSIAN)
Faster. faster!
GOD'S EYE TECH:
The motorcade just turned on Seventh.
CIPHER: Perfect. Make it rain.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Ah!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(IN RUSSIAN)
Oh. God!
Target immobilized.
You're up. Dom.
(IN RUSSIAN)
What the hell is that?
What's he doing?
What are you waiting for?
Shoot him!
Come on. come on!
I'm out.
Shit.
Don't worry. sir.
The car is impenetrable.
You'll be safe in here.
(BOTH GRUNT)
- DOM: (IN ENGLISH) Give me the case.
- (IN RUSSIAN)
Give him the case!
Those are nuclear launch codes.
We cannot give it to him.
What is he doing?
He just cut a hole in our gas tank!
(TAPPING)
(PANTING)
(RUSSIAN SECRET SERVICE AGENT PANTING)
(IN ENGLISH) Good work. Dom.
Meet you at the pickup.
(TIRES SCREECH)
DOM: I think I know where my team's at.
- Where?
- Right in front of me.
This is on you.
Get out of there. Dom.
RAMSEY: (OVER RADIO)
Guys. I know why Dom's here.
Police scanners are saying
he stole a nuclear football.
(OVER SPEAKERS) It's over. Toretto.
Get your ass outta the car now.
(ENGINE REVVING)
So. that's how you wanna play this?
Let's play.
Don't do this. Dom.
He's going for it!
- What are you doing?
- It's a trap!
Damn it!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
TEJ: Now I know what it feels like
to be every cop ever chasing us!
I'm gonna get a little closer.
I'm gonna PIT him.
Oh. so. you just gonna PIT Dom?
Little Nobody has clearly
lost his little mind.
I'm on him.
Easy. Work together.
(MEN YELLING)
Wait. wait. wait!
Oh. sh...
I'll take the shortcut!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
RAMSEY: Look out! Watch those people!
Big Sexy comin' through!
Not this time. Dom.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Watch the drag or the line will snap!
(GRUNTING)
Stretch him out! Hold him!
(GRUNTS)
He's gotta have about
2.000 horsepower in that thing.
Try 3.000!
Try five.
Get out of there.
I'm working on it.
CIPHER: Stop working on it and do it.
No. no. no. this my Bentley!
(YELLING)
No! No!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Get that case and run.
(GRUNTS)
Move.
They thought this was
gonna be a street fight.
What are you waiting for. Toretto?
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
No!
(SIREN WAILING)
(SIGHS)
Letty. stop!
What are you gonna do?
(GASPS)
I don't know why you're doing this.
but I know one thing.
You love me.
And you are not gonna shoot me.
You should've given him the case.
'cause I won't chase you.
Okay.
I will just take it from a dead girl.
DOM: You willing to die for it?
Let's go. then.
HOBBS: Anything?
They're gone.
And DOD confirmed it was a nuclear football.
He's got an EMP and nuclear launch codes.
I don't know what it is.
but they're building towards something.
Deckard?
LITTLE NOBODY: He didn't make it.
(GRUNTS)
CIPHER: (OVER INTERCOM)
I'm disappointed in you. Dom.
When push came to shove. you were gonna
let Letty just walk away with the codes.
You got the codes!
Rhodes got the codes.
You made the choice to let her go.
And now I have to make one of my own.
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
(WHISPERING) They are adorable
little things. aren't they?
God. I hope I don't hurt him.
Look. psychotic. I did exactly
what you asked me to do.
Don't do this.
This is your doing.
My doing?
BABY TORETTO: (BABBLING) Da-dada.
Dada.
Da-da.
Please don't hurt him. I'm begging you.
I don't want you to beg.
I want you to learn.
Learn what?
I understand why you did
what you did. I really do.
Da-da.
But it was the wrong choice.
This is the consequence of that.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING) No!
No! No!
Wait. wait. wait. Wait.
Save your son!
No!
(GUNSHOTS)
(CRYING)
(SHUSHING)
(EXHALES)
Can you pull up the footage
from the guy in the alley?
Traffic cams.
I got you.
I knew it.
I recognize that guy.
That's Connor Rhodes.
I met him when I was working
with Shaw's brother.
He wanted us to get
the Nightshade device for him.
Connor Rhodes.
He's also linked to somebody
I'd quite like to forget.
It's Mose Jakande.
Warlord who tried to get God's Eye.
Which means that's twice that Dom
has messed up Cipher's business.
Everything you're feeling right now.
this rage. a sense of loss. it's not real.
It's a survival instinct
wired deep into our brains
to ensure continuation of the species.
When early man would visit a watering hole.
if they didn't watch their child.
and it got snatched by a crocodile.
our brains would create
a painful but instructional memory.
so it would never happen again.
This idea of "family"
that is so core with you.
that rules your world.
it's a biological lie.
You don't have to accept it.
I don't.
Did you really think you
could destroy two of my teams
without any repercussions?
I wouldn't have even looked
your way if you hadn't done that.
You didn't even know you had a kid.
You can thank me for that and start
doing the job I'm asking you to do.
Help you start a war.
Is that what you think I want?
That's so limited.
I didn't take that football to start a war
any more than I took
your son to start a family.
Taking your son got me the codes.
The codes will get me the nukes
and the nukes will get me what I want
today. tomorrow. and every day after that.
And what's that?
Accountability.
The second I fire off one of those nukes.
I put the superpowers
of this world on notice that.
when they cross the line.
I'm gonna be there to hold them responsible.
Because the truth is. Dom.
to the world out there.
I am the crocodile at the watering hole.
We've got one last job to do.
DOM: Cipher.
If I were you. I'd kiss my son.
Because whether
you value it or not. all of this.
your plane. your security. and you.
are still on this earth because of him.
RAMSEY: The problem we've had with
tracking Cipher is there's nothing to trace.
But now. we have Rhodes' information.
And we're getting snapshots of his data
before it's scrubbed off the net.
That looks like somebody's bank account.
so why don't we just go ahead...
It's a longitude.
Given the fact that Dom
hit a Russian motorcade.
it's safe to say it's Russia.
Go ahead and bring up the map.
Good. Let's start here
and run the possibilities.
Yalta. Poltava...
It's like they just threw letters together.
Kronyurt.
MR. NOBODY: It's "Vladovin."
- What are you doing here?
- What?
Told you I was gonna check in on you from
time to time to see how you were doin'.
By the way. not so hot.
But there's nothing in Vladovin.
It's just ice.
That's funny.
Could've sworn there was
a secret Russian naval base
where they retrofitted Cold War submarines.
Well. technically. it's not Russian anymore.
The base was taken over
by a terror group of military
separatists about a month ago.
and the Russians haven't taken it back yet.
so there is a little window
of opportunity here.
Russian submarines. Nuclear football.
It sounds like everything we do.
our legs gonna be blown off.
It sounds like you still
number 11 on the list. (CHUCKLES)
It sounds like you've changed
since your little punk-ass
facial hairs done came in.
Guys. guys.
Hey. we gotta call this in.
All the way up the chain.
That's good thinking. champ.
except unfortunately.
the Russian Minister of Defense
got himself involved in a little
incident on US territory.
and the two governments aren't talking
to each other for a while.
By the time they do. it'll be too late.
So. any other suggestions?
HOBBS: Yeah. I got one.
How about we just stop them ourselves?
You're talking about a Russian military base.
Separatist.
Whatever. It's suicide.
It's stopping World War III.
What's it gonna be. rook?
You gonna close your eyes on this one. too?
Pray that the apocalypse doesn't come
knocking on your mama's front door?
Or. are you gonna saddle up. be a man.
and save the entire goddamn world?
You know. I think I figured it out.
What's that?
- Rule number three.
- Which is?
There are no rules.
(MR. NOBODY LAUGHS)
What'd I tell you. Luke?
I knew he'd get it in three.
LITTLE NOBODY:
Aerial transport leaves in an hour.
Take whatever vehicle you want.
All bets are off.
- All bets are off?
- Bets are off?
Do svidanya!
Letty. I don't like telling you this one bit.
But the game's changed.
Before. we were just trying to catch Dom.
but now. after all this.
I want you to know. if I have to.
I'm gonna put him down.
Then you might have to take us both down.
ROMAN: I'm freezing. man.
(BREATHING HEAVILY) This ain't for me.
I come from a different
kind of lifestyle. brah.
Ladies know me.
They know where I'm at with it.
I tried to take a piss.
I didn't even recognize myself.
Man. that's entirely too much information.
I'm just sayin'.
Well. one thing's for sure.
Dom's gotta be either working
with them or making a trade.
because no one would be this insane
to hit this place without a damn army.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
HOBBS: Speak of the devil.
All right. Dom. you're one step
closer to that family reunion.
400 meters to base.
Prep the EMP. Let's take these defenses down.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
We have a possible threat approaching.
Raise the barricade.
We've lost power. defensive positions now.
(CLAPS) (IN ENGLISH) Gates are open.
Let's get this party started.
(SOLDIERS YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
- EMP is recharging.
- How long?
Sixty seconds.
All right. Dom. you have
one pulse left in that EMP.
That sub is heavily insulated.
You're gonna need to be right
underneath it for this thing to work.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(GRUNTING)
- Come on.
- (SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Engaging target. He's beneath the sub.
(ALARMS BLARING)
Mayday! Mayday! I've lost all power.
I'm going down.
CIPHER: Yes!
Two birds with one stone.
SUPER JET TECH: We've got control of the sub.
Dom. we are good.
Head over to the rendezvous.
Okay. Matty. let's take this baby for a spin.
TEJ: Damn!
I think Cipher just rebooted that
sub to slave its command system.
What the hell is he talking about?
In layman's terms.
she just carjacked a submarine.
We can't let it get away.
There's the control room.
If you can get me into that wheelhouse.
I can tap the network
and counter-hack Cipher.
Keep it from lowering into the water.
No. what we need to do is get me on that sub.
I find the weapons room
and I can pull the launch chip
before she can fire any of those nukes.
That is too crazy.
What you're saying is too dangerous.
We'll do both.
Knock. knock.
(SOLDIERS YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Five vehicles just breached the base.
They just don't give up. do they?
HOBBS: All right. let's haul ass. team.
Double time. double time!
(SOLDIERS YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
(YELLING)
Letty. let's roll!
(GROANS)
Go! Go. go. go!
CIPHER: Change of plans. Dom.
I'm sending you new coordinates.
Head there immediately.
I'm done. I want my son.
I'll tell you when you're done.
Your team is in play.
Now. meet Rhodes and follow my instruction.
(PANTING)
I've got you covered! Go!
Move. move! Get outta here! Go. go. go!
(PANTING)
Okay. How do you like this?
(ENGINE POWERING DOWN)
- JET TECH: Remote link has been severed.
- CIPHER: I'll take care of this.
Hi. Ramsey.
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
RAMSEY: She's regained control.
Damn it. She's good.
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
TECH: They're entering the weapons room.
Oh. that's cute.
LITTLE NOBODY: (EXCLAIMS) Pull! Pull!
Roman. Roman! We gotta find the chip. go!
Oh. she's slick.
Gonna have to do better than that. though.
Okay. now you're starting to piss me off.
(GRUNTING)
(MAN YELLING)
Ramsey. how much time we talkin' here?
You're smart. but not smart enough.
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
She's locked me out.
(GRUNTING)
Tej. I can't stop her.
You're gonna have to pull that chip.
I can't! This thing's gone into attack mode!
The door's not gonna open
until you pull the chip!
Tej. we got no idea
what the hell we're looking for.
I got it!
(ALARM BLARING)
What in the hell are you guys doin'?
It wasn't me. It wasn't me. okay?
It'll be labeled "Guidance Go."
- Guidance Go. Guidance Go...
- Okay. I got somethin'.
- What?
- It says...
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
Do you understand that?
(GROANING)
(MAN LAUGHING)
- (YELLING)
- (SPLATTERING)
(PANTING)
Wow. Nasty.
Hmm.
Quite a show.
We're arming the nuke.
(POWERING UP)
TEJ: (OVER RADIO) Nuke's going hot!
She's tryin' to fire this thing!
Roger that. We're moving out.
(OVER RADIO) Disable the nukes!
Roman. what are you seeing?
Come on. talk to me.
I don't see shit. I'm holding on!
(RUMBLING)
And we have a countdown.
(ALARM BLARING)
What the hell is goin' on. man?
We're about to launch a nuclear missile.
is what the hell is goin' on!
Pull the damn chip!
(PANTING)
Countdown. countdown! Look for a countdown!
What countdown?
The missiles need to activate to launch.
The countdown timer won't be in Russian.
The countdown...
Let's show the world what we've got.
ROMAN: No. no. no! Don't press that!
I got it.
Something's wrong. It won't launch.
Get that sub outta there. Now!
LITTLE NOBODY: Move your ass. Roman!
(PANTING)
You all right?
There's nothing all right about any of this!
- Let's go!
- What about the missiles?
We got the chip. No nukes for her.
Hell. yeah. Let's roll.
Guys. we got company. A lot of company!
All right. team. here's the plan.
There's a sea lock at the opening of the bay.
We get there first and close it.
we can stop the submarine
from escaping into open water
and disappearing forever.
I've got the location.
It's 10 miles southwest.
Ten miles?
We're not gonna make it ten seconds!
(GUNFIRE)
Ah!
No. no. no! This is not good!
What's the matter. Roman?
Forgot your snow tires?
ROMAN: Whoa!
You lovin' that Lambo now?
ROMAN: Whoa! Ah!
(ROMAN EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMING)
CIPHER: All right. everyone.
We'll deal with that launch chip later.
Right now. I want that sub
in deep water where no one can find it.
Find me the fastest route out of that bay.
Copy that.
Why are they shootin' at me?
Maybe 'cause you're in an orange
Lamborghini. I don't know.
Shut up. Tej!
Dom...
(OVER EARPIECE)
Do you really wanna put that car in gear?
Do it.
Huh?
I didn't think so.
They're heading for the sea lock.
They're trying to trap the sub in the bay.
I should have taken care
of this a long time ago.
Rhodes. take his team out.
I'm on it.
Roman. get in front of me!
Okay. y'all wanna play rough?
Now it's my turn.
Yeah. baby! (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS)
Guys. we got snowmobiles on the right.
They're gonna flank us!
No. they ain't!
Oh. shit!
(BEEPING)
Tej!
Roman. hold tight. I'm on the way!
I don't wanna go swimmin'! No!
Really. Tej?
Oh. no. no. no!
Oh. shit!
Roman. grab your door!
ROMAN: Tej!
TEJ: Grab the door. Roman!
- ROMAN: It's so cold!
- Shit!
Oh. shit!
ROMAN: Whoa!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
What is going on?
Roman. hang on!
Tej!
Get me off of this thing!
Come on!
Argh!
All right. I've had enough of this shit!
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(ALL GROANING)
Number 11. my ass!
Yo. shrinkage! We got a sub to catch. Get in!
What?
Depressurization alert in the cargo hold.
Drop it to 10.000 feet.
I know how much these people mean to you.
So I will let you pick the first target.
I don't pick a target from a mile away.
I stand face to face
and look 'em dead in the eye.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
The wife it is.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Nice plane. I'm gonna enjoy having this.
Hey. don't go gettin' any ideas.
You and planes don't have a good history.
No shit.
Okay. let's go. Scarface.
These assholes ain't gonna kill themselves.
Pull up surveillance right now.
(COMPUTER TRILLS)
Surprise.
You're supposed to be dead.
(IN SPANISH)
You're driving.
- I said from the beginning...
- No way.
- I am not going to drive.
- I'm not driving.
We have a security breach in
the cargo hold. Take care of it now.
(GASPS)
Jesus. Mum.
You're supposed to avoid the nerves.
Oh. shut up. Don't be such a baby.
Get to the pilot.
He's got the second key. Wait for my signal.
Give Cipher my regards.
Did Toretto hold up his end of the deal?
MRS. SHAW: He gave us this little thing here.
No. no. no. Don't touch.
You can track Cipher with this.
but you can't do this on your own.
There's gotta be two of ya.
Fine. I've got contacts.
No. you're gonna take your brother.
- Oh. dear...
- Yes.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Toretto knows where he is.
He's got this thing. It can see everything.
It's like... It's called
the Devil's Bum Hole or something.
It's called the God's Eye.
Yeah. well. whatever.
(GRUNTING)
There's no way I'm using Owen. all right?
He's a lost cause.
He's your brother. Decks. He's my son.
He's our family.
And our family don't die in bloody cages.
(CRYING)
How can you talk like that about Owen?
I can't believe you.
You've gone and upset me.
You've really upset your mother.
Call yourself a brother? You're...
Look. come here... Mum. Okay. okay.
Every time.
Owen.
In position.
Go.
I'm in.
(PANTING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
DECKARD: I've got the package. Toretto.
All 12 pounds of him.
Ah.
Dada. Dada.
- (BULLET RICOCHETS)
- (BOTH GASP)
You made me miss my shot.
What you think you're doing?
Looking at you dead in the eye.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GAGGING)
(YELLING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (NECK SNAPS)
That was for Elena.
Rhodes.
DOM: He's no longer with us.
Rhodes picked the wrong target.
Congratulations. Dom.
You just killed your son.
You're wrong. I just saved him.
And you just took your foot
off the tiger's neck.
All right. governor. it's gonna get noisy.
This is for your ears.
(BEEPS)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
Good?
(COOS)
Let's go.
No! Stop him!
Do not let him get off this plane!
LITTLE NOBODY: We got another problem.
That truck's got
enough missiles to take us all out.
Then don't give 'em a target.
Everybody. get in front of us.
line up. and we'll take the hit.
What? I need to switch cars right now!
(IN RUSSIAN)
Target acquired.
- Roman. here comes the bad part.
- What?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(WHOOPS)
Hang in there. guys.
We're almost to the lock.
It's easy for you to say
when your ass ain't on fire.
All right. little man.
this might be a little scary.
but it's gonna be a lot of fun.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
How's the music. good?
Ah.
(ALL GROANING)
They're locking on.
Sorry. guys. I got no tricks left.
What do we do now?
TEJ: We start prayin'!
Hell. yeah!
There's Dom!
What. is this guy on our side now?
Who the hell cares? He just saved our ass!
Good to be riding with you again. man.
(CHUCKLES)
Toretto just cleared the way for them.
Someone. give me something!
Torpedoes are ready.
Then launch them!
Shit.
- Take the wheel!
- I ain't takin' shit!
Take the wheel!
Where you goin'?
(GROANS)
This is crazy!
HOBBS: Speed up!
- Left and back!
- What?
Turn the goddamn wheel
to the left really quickly!
Boom. baby!
(MEN GRUNTING)
Goin' for a ride.
Back in a sec.
(ALL GRUNTING)
- Where's that smile?
- Ah.
There it is.
You were gonna shoot a baby?
You sick bastard.
You're not gonna wanna see this.
(GRUNTING)
(SNIFFS)
Is that you or him?
Him. Good.
The torpedoes missed.
They're gonna reach the lock
before the sub does.
The hell they are.
Get ready for this.
Oh. shit!
We're gonna need a bigger truck.
(LAUGHING)
It's right under us! Get out the way!
(GRUNTING)
Get us out of here!
Why are you always yelling?
This bitch is crazy!
- Look out!
- (GASPS)
(YELLS)
That's not good.
Please tell me there's nothing
to worry about!
We got this.
(YELLS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SIGHS)
(LAUGHS)
(PANTING)
That's my girl.
The sub's too close.
We ain't making it to the gate in time.
We're just going to let it get away?
Not if I know Dom.
You lose. Dom.
I destroyed two of your teams.
I killed your red-headed boyfriend.
And I put two killers
on your untraceable plane.
You lost the minute
you interrupted my honeymoon.
Now guess who I'm coming for.
Put a heatseeker on him now.
(SHOUTS) Now!
Fire!
That's a goddamn heatseeker coming at us!
Peel off! Head to the shore!
- (BEEPING)
- (ENGINE REVVING)
All right. Come and get it.
No. no. no.
Dive! Dive!
This...
This is for my son.
(GASPS)
Dom!
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR OPENS)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (MAN GROANS)
You're out of bullets. Deckard.
Not like I'm gonna need a gun
to take care of you.
How did you find me?
DOM: You want to see the old Dom?
- (BEEPING)
- Watch.
Resourceful.
You have a lot to answer for. Cipher.
What you've put my family through.
My mother.
I'm gonna make sure that never happens again.
To anyone.
There is only one flaw in your plan.
What's that?
Only one of us has a parachute.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(COOING)
Told you this would be fun.
Time to land. boys.
You know I never left you. Letty.
I know.
And you know I never will.
(LAUGHS)
(PANTING)
I have so much to tell you.
Yeah. you do.
And you can start with that bitch.
Now. that's Dominic Toretto.
Hey. Dom!
I'm just throwin' it out there.
we need to get up outta here
'cause there's all kinda nuclearism
happening under this ice.
Relax. Without the trigger chips.
those nukes are harmless.
Okay. So we good. then.
Let me go on and get
my young selfie levels up.
You realize this is classified. right?
Not today.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
Unbelievable.
All right. can we get up
outta here. now? I'm freezin'!
It's okay.
Don't worry. He's gonna be here soon.
ROMAN: I get it. Y'all got a lot in common.
Computer hacks. God's Eye.
geeks. nerd... You know.
But we got a lot in common. too. right?
Like what?
We walk in the room
and we're oozin' sex appeal.
Me and you. hip to hip. is a problem.
I'm askin' a real question right now.
Is it gonna be Revenge of the Nerds
or The Dark Knight? Huh?
To be honest. I like both of you.
(ROMAN AND TEJ EXCLAIMING)
But just before we get into all of that.
let me ask you one question.
You can ask me anything.
Anything.
What's my last name?
When you guys figure it out.
then. I guess you can let me know.
It's gonna be Parker.
That's all that really matters.
- ROMAN: Jones.
- TEJ: Mrs. Parker.
- Right?
- Hey. Mrs. Parker...
LETTY: Hey.
Letty.
I wanted to thank you.
No need.
Well...
Cipher's still on the loose.
There's been some reports she's in Athens.
but she won't be nuking
any cities anytime soon.
Thanks to you guys.
So. I got you a party favor.
- (MR. NOBODY LAUGHS)
- HOBBS: This can't be good.
Your record's been cleared.
Full reinstatement.
You've got your job back.
That is. if you want it.
If I want?
Mmm-hmm.
(LAUGHS)
You know. after 16 years.
I figure it's time for a little break.
Wow.
Daddy's stayin' home.
(LAUGHS)
Nobody.
Keep in touch.
Ah. Hang on a second.
This could be interesting.
(SIGHS) What made you think I'd do it?
Brotherhood.
I saw that look you gave Cipher.
knew you wanted revenge.
Glad I did it.
I can't believe you went to see my mother.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
All this fuss over you.
(COOING)
Yes.
Elena. I promised to keep our son safe.
And now. he always will be.
I wanna introduce you to the most
important person in my universe.
One who never gave up on me.
He's beautiful.
DOM: You've heard me say that you
never turn your back on family.
and I wanna thank you all
for never turning your back on me.
You wanna meet them?
All right.
Everyone.
meet Brian.
(LAUGHTER. APPLAUSE)
(COOING)
HOBBS: To Brian!
ROMAN: Welcome to the family. Brian.
Okay. I guess it's my turn to say grace.
We thank you for giving us family.
We sit here in praise.
Thank you for giving us the strength...
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-